Bernard C. Smith Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subject Files, 1963-1969; Undated; nam_apap279-1; 9.75 cu. ft.
  - Pension Bills, 1968; nam_apap279-1_262 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Pension Fund, 1968; nam_apap279-1_263 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Personal, 1968; nam_apap279-1_264 (Box 6, Folder 45-46)
  - Personal, 1968-1969; nam_apap279-1_265 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Personal, 1969; nam_apap279-1_266 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pesticides, 1969; nam_apap279-1_267 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Pharmacist, 1968; nam_apap279-1_268 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pharmacy, 1969; nam_apap279-1_269 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Physicians, 1968; nam_apap279-1_270 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Physiotherapists, 1968; nam_apap279-1_271 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pilgrim State Hospital, 1969; nam_apap279-1_272 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Plumbers, 1968; nam_apap279-1_273 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Podiatry Bill, 1968; nam_apap279-1_274 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Podiatry Practice Act, 1969; nam_apap279-1_275 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Police File, 1967-1968; nam_apap279-1_276 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Pollution Control Law, 1969; nam_apap279-1_277 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Pornographic Material, 1966-1967; nam_apap279-1_278 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Pornographic Material, 1969; nam_apap279-1_279 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Power Program, 1968; Undated; nam_apap279-1_280 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Primary, 1969; nam_apap279-1_281 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Press Clippings, 1968; nam_apap279-1_282 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Press Clippings, 1969; nam_apap279-1_283 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1968; Undated; nam_apap279-1_284 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1969; nam_apap279-1_285 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Principal Salary Bill, 1968; nam_apap279-1_286 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Principals' Salary Bill, 1969; nam_apap279-1_287 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Professional Engineers, 1968; nam_apap279-1_288 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Professional Nurses, 1966-1968; nam_apap279-1_289 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Psychology, 1969; nam_apap279-1_290 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Public Disclosure File, 1968; nam_apap279-1_291 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Public Health, Undated; nam_apap279-1_292 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Public Health Law, 1966-1968; nam_apap279-1_293 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Public Housing, 1969; nam_apap279-1_294 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Public Works, 1969; nam_apap279-1_295 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Pure Waters, 1969; nam_apap279-1_296 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Questionnaire, 1967-1968; Undated; nam_apap279-1_297 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Questionnaire, 1969; nam_apap279-1_298 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Quarter Horse Racing, 1965-1967; nam_apap279-1_299 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Racing Association, 1968; nam_apap279-1_300 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Raceway, 1969; nam_apap279-1_301 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Rain Maker, 1968; nam_apap279-1_302 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Railroads, 1968; nam_apap279-1_303 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Regents College Scholarships, 1966-1968; nam_apap279-1_304 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Regents Scholarship Winners, 1966; 1968; nam_apap279-1_305 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Rehabilitation, 1968; nam_apap279-1_306 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Rehabilitation, 1969; nam_apap279-1_307 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Rent Control, 1968; nam_apap279-1_308 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Report: "Annual Report of the State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance", 1965; nam_apap279-1_309 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Report: "Facts About Nurses and Nursing in New York State" Office of Nurse Education, 1966; nam_apap279-1_310 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Report: "Federal Aid and Tax Sharing", 1967; nam_apap279-1_311 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Report: "New York State and Higher Education", 1968; nam_apap279-1_312 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Report: "Office of Economic Opportunity Information Center, Community Profile: Suffolk County", Undated; nam_apap279-1_313 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Report: "Poverty and Economic Development in New York City", 1968; nam_apap279-1_314 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Report: "Professional and Employment Characteristics of Professional Nurses Registered in New York State" SUNY, NY State Education Dept., 1966; nam_apap279-1_315 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Report: "State of New York Dept of Public Works - In the Matter of a Hearing Held to Consider the Proposed Reconstruction of Jericho Turnpike…", Undated; nam_apap279-1_316 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Report: "State of New York Insurance Dept: Fees and Taxes Charged Insurance Companies.", 1968; nam_apap279-1_317 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Report: "Tax Overlapping in the United States", 1966; nam_apap279-1_318 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Report: "Transcript of Minutes of a Public Hearing of the Senate Finance Sub-Committee…", 1968; nam_apap279-1_319 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Report: "The New York State Budget for 1968-69: A Review and Report.", nam_apap279-1_320 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Report: "The Striped Bass - A Game Fish in New York State." by Frederick Schwab, 1969; nam_apap279-1_321 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Report: "The Taylor Law", 1969; nam_apap279-1_322 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Republic Airfield, 1968; nam_apap279-1_323 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Republic Airport, 1969; nam_apap279-1_324 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Requests, 1968; nam_apap279-1_325 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Requests, 1969; nam_apap279-1_326 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Research - Human, 1969; nam_apap279-1_327 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Resolution 72 - Pornographic Obscene Literature, 1969; nam_apap279-1_328 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Richard Spera, 1966; nam_apap279-1_329 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Rodeos, 1967; nam_apap279-1_330 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Route 25A, 1969; nam_apap279-1_331 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Route 110A, 1969; nam_apap279-1_332 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Route 110 - Jericho, 1966-1968; nam_apap279-1_333 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Sagtikos Manor Historical Society, 1967; nam_apap279-1_334 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Salesman Bill, 1969; nam_apap279-1_335 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Sale of Meat, 1968; nam_apap279-1_336 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Sales Tax, 1966-1967; nam_apap279-1_337 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Sales Tax, 1969; nam_apap279-1_338 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Sanitarians, 1968; nam_apap279-1_339 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - School Aid, 1969; nam_apap279-1_340 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - School Athletic Program Bill, 1969; nam_apap279-1_341 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - School Board Teacher Relations Bill, 1967; nam_apap279-1_342 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - School Bus Transportation, 1967; nam_apap279-1_343 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - School Districts, 1967-1968; Undated; nam_apap279-1_344 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - School Lunch, 1968; nam_apap279-1_345 (Box 8, Folder 36-37)
  - Senate Standing Committee on Taxation, 1968; nam_apap279-1_346 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Senior Citizen, 1968; nam_apap279-1_347 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Senior Citizen Tax Bill, 1969; nam_apap279-1_348 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Sewage System, 1967; nam_apap279-1_349 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Social Security, 1969; nam_apap279-1_350 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Social Services, Undated; nam_apap279-1_351 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Social Services, 1969; nam_apap279-1_352 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Social Services Law, 1968; Undated; nam_apap279-1_353 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Social Welfare [1 of 2], 1966-1967; nam_apap279-1_354 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Social Welfare [2 of 2], 1967-1968; nam_apap279-1_355 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Social Workers, 1968; nam_apap279-1_356 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Southhold Signs, 1966; Undated; nam_apap279-1_357 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - South Mall, 1969; nam_apap279-1_358 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Speech, 1968; Undated; nam_apap279-1_359 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Speech Material, 1968; nam_apap279-1_360 (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
  - Speech Material, 1969; nam_apap279-1_361 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - State Budget Cutback Letters and Telegrams, 1969; nam_apap279-1_362 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
  - State Education Department File, 1968; nam_apap279-1_363 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - State Liquor Authority, 1967; nam_apap279-1_364 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - State Police, 1968; nam_apap279-1_365 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - State Revenue, 1967-1968; nam_apap279-1_366 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - State University, 1969; nam_apap279-1_367 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Statistics, Undated; nam_apap279-1_368 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Statute of Limitations, Undated; nam_apap279-1_369 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Statute of Limitations Bill, 1967; nam_apap279-1_370 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Steuben Society of America, 1968; nam_apap279-1_371 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Striped Bass Game Fish Bill, 1969; nam_apap279-1_372 (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
  - Subsidies to Builders, Plumbers, 1966; nam_apap279-1_373 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Suffolk County, 1969; nam_apap279-1_374 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Suffolk County Hearing and Speech Center, 1967; nam_apap279-1_375 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Suffolk County Organization for the Promotion of Education (SCOPE), 1969; nam_apap279-1_376 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - Suffolk County Schools Listing, Undated; nam_apap279-1_377 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Suffolk County Water Authority, 1967; nam_apap279-1_378 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Suffolk State School (Melville), 1966-1968; nam_apap279-1_379 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Supreme Court Judges, 1968; nam_apap279-1_380 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Syracuse University, 1969; nam_apap279-1_381 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Tax Budget, 1968; nam_apap279-1_382 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Taxation - General Information, 1965-1968; nam_apap279-1_383 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Taxes, 1966-1968; nam_apap279-1_384 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Taxes, 1968; nam_apap279-1_385 (Box 9, Folder 35-36)
  - Taxes, 1969; nam_apap279-1_386 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Taylor Act, 1968; nam_apap279-1_387 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Taylor Law, 1969; nam_apap279-1_388 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Teacher Retirement, 1968; nam_apap279-1_389 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
  - Teacher Retirement, 1969; nam_apap279-1_390 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Teacher Salary Bill, 1967; nam_apap279-1_391 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Telephone, New York State, 1968; nam_apap279-1_392 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "The Thoroughbred Record and the Racing Calendar" (Publication), 1967; nam_apap279-1_393 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Town Law, 1969; nam_apap279-1_394 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Town of Islip, 1968; nam_apap279-1_395 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Town of Islip, 1969; nam_apap279-1_396 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Traffic Light, 1969; nam_apap279-1_397 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Traffic Safety, 1968; nam_apap279-1_398 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Transit, New York City, 1966; nam_apap279-1_399 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority, 1967; nam_apap279-1_400 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Tuition, 1969; nam_apap279-1_401 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Unemployment Insurance Plan, 1968; nam_apap279-1_402 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Utilities, 1969; nam_apap279-1_403 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Utilities and Rules, 1967-1969; nam_apap279-1_404 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Urban Development, 1968; nam_apap279-1_405 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Veterans, 1969; nam_apap279-1_406 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Veterinary, 1969; nam_apap279-1_407 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Village of Port Jefferson, 1969; nam_apap279-1_408 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Village Law, 1968; nam_apap279-1_409 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Village of Patchogue, 1969; nam_apap279-1_410 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1968; nam_apap279-1_411 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1969; nam_apap279-1_412 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Vocational Education, 1968; nam_apap279-1_413 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Welfare, 1967-1968; nam_apap279-1_414 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Welfare, 1969; nam_apap279-1_415 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Wild River, 1968-1969; nam_apap279-1_416 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Wiretap, 1969; nam_apap279-1_417 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Working Notes on Highway Package, 1966-1968; nam_apap279-1_418 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1968; nam_apap279-1_419 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Wire Tapping, 1968; nam_apap279-1_420 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Youth Programs, 1963-1966; nam_apap279-1_421 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Bills, 1967-1968; nam_apap279-2; .65 cu. ft.
  Arranged chronologically by bill number.
  Series 2, Bills, features files for pertaining to each of the bills that Smith introduced in the State Senate 1968.
  - S. 262, Social Ser. Law, restrict assist. For persons not having state residence, 1968; nam_apap279-2_1 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - S. 377, Penal Law, forfeiture of vessel, veh., aircraft in trans. gambling devices, 1968; nam_apap279-2_2 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - S. 379, Education Law, approval of drainage for schools (new or add), 1968; nam_apap279-2_3 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - S. 380, Education Law, School fire alarms, 1968; nam_apap279-2_4 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - S. 430, Education Law, levying tax non-prof. salaries, 1968; nam_apap279-2_5 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - S. 432, Highway Law, consultation Supt. Of public work and local governing bodies in planning State Highway proj., 1967-1968; nam_apap279-2_6 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - S. 433, Highway Law, designation of State highways in Suffolk, 1968; nam_apap279-2_7 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - S. 434, Real Prop. Tax Law, income of persons over 65, eligible for partial exemption, 1968; nam_apap279-2_8 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - S.884, Town Law-improve Dists., payments, 1968; nam_apap279-2_9 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - S. 1021, Navig. Law-outboard motors, sales, 1968; nam_apap279-2_10 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - S. 1179, Multi-Sponsored, Educ., educ. Dept. review board, 1968; nam_apap279-2_11 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - S. 1234, Soc. Services Laws-work relief assigns, 1968; nam_apap279-2_12 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - S. 1235, Soc. Services Law-priv. nursing homes, 1968; nam_apap279-2_13 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - S. 1360, Penal Law-gambling devices seizures, 1968; nam_apap279-2_14 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - S. 1378, Navig. Law-water skiing, regulations, 1968; nam_apap279-2_15 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - S. 1380, Education Law - NYC, School construction, 1968; nam_apap279-2_16 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - S. 1381, Election Law - absentee voting, 1968; nam_apap279-2_17 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - S. 1489, Gen. Municipal Law - officers, fin. Interest, 1968; nam_apap279-2_18 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - S. 1505, An act in relation to assess and coll. Of taxes in Suffolk Co., 1968; nam_apap279-2_19 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - S. 1566, Tax Law - local reality transfer taxes, 1967-1968; nam_apap279-2_20 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - S. 1598, Penal Law - oper. And main. Radio receiving sets - regulations, 1968; nam_apap279-2_21 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - S. 1758, Retire. and Soc. Security Law - final salary of policemen and firemen, 1968; nam_apap279-2_22 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - S. 1759, Public off. Law - leave of absence for vet., 1968; nam_apap279-2_23 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - S. 1859, Multi- Sponsored, Educ., state aid apportionment, 1968; nam_apap279-2_24 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - S. 1860, Multi- Sponsored, Educ., state aid apportionment, 1968; nam_apap279-2_25 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - S. 1890, Civil Serv. - veterans/ preference, 1968; nam_apap279-2_26 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - S. 2139, Banking Law - aggregate unpaid loans, 1968; nam_apap279-2_27 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - S. 2203, Banking Law - Saving bks., investments, 1968; nam_apap279-2_28 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - S. 2220, Banking Law - Personal Loan departments, 1968; nam_apap279-2_29 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - S. 2308, Penal Law - physical force in defense, 1968; nam_apap279-2_30 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - S. 2309, Public Health Law- funeral students, 1968; nam_apap279-2_31 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - S. 2364, Metro. Transport, auth. Reality taxes, 1968; nam_apap279-2_32 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - S. 2365, Retire. and Soc. Sec. Law - Suffolk Co., Sheriff. Retire, 1968; nam_apap279-2_33 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - S. 2366, Retire. SS, sheriffs, under-sheriffs, 1968; nam_apap279-2_34 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - S. 2367, Educ., schl. Construction actions, 1968; nam_apap279-2_35 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - S. 2512, Melville Vol. Firemen's Assn., 1968; nam_apap279-2_36 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - S. 2527, Bank., office location changes, 1968; nam_apap279-2_37 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - S. 2528, Savings., loan assns., home mtg. loans., 1968; nam_apap279-2_38 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - S. 2530, Suffolk Co., addl. County judge, 1968; nam_apap279-2_39 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - S. 2531, Suffolk Co., addl. Family ct. judge, 1968; nam_apap279-2_40 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - S. 2619, Judy., 10th dist., supr. Ct. judges, 1968; nam_apap279-2_41 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - S. 2894, Greenlawn Vol. Firemen's Assn., 1968; nam_apap279-2_42 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - S. 2953, Education Law- landscape architecture, 1968; nam_apap279-2_43 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - S. 3261, Per. Prop. Law - home solicit, contracts, 1968; nam_apap279-2_44 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - S. 3346, Navig. Law - boat liveries, regulns, 1968; nam_apap279-2_45 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - S. 3347, Navig. Law - pleasure boats, markings, 1968; nam_apap279-2_46 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - S. 3348, Navig. Law - water skiers, regulns., 1968; nam_apap279-2_47 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - S. 3350, Criminal Code - Suffolk Co., cert. loc. Police, powers, 1968; nam_apap279-2_48 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - S. 3429, State Park police, medical care, 1968; nam_apap279-2_49 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - S. 3430, dpts. Educ., County Library, 1968; nam_apap279-2_50 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - S. 3431, Educ., Practice of Pharmacy, 1968; nam_apap279-2_51 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - S. 3469, Bank., banks, net profits, 1968; nam_apap279-2_52 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - S. 3586, Navig. Boats, beaching, regulations, 1968; nam_apap279-2_53 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - S. 3633, Navig., boats, pollution controls, 1968; nam_apap279-2_54 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - S. 3634, Nassau co., drug addict boat drivers, 1968; nam_apap279-2_55 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - S. 3649, Multi-Sponsored, Elect., electors' certificates, 1968; nam_apap279-2_56 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - S. 3675, Deer Park Vol. Firemen's Assn., 1968; nam_apap279-2_57 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - S. 3684, Educ., certain schl. Dist. Voters, 1968; nam_apap279-2_58 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - S. 3762, Suffolk Co. police, retirements, 1968; nam_apap279-2_59 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - S. 3763, Conserv., health insur. Plan, 1968; nam_apap279-2_60 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - S. 3765, Tax, sales, use tax collectors, 1968; nam_apap279-2_61 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - S. 3766, Tax, sales, use tax credits, refunds, 1968; nam_apap279-2_62 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - S. 3767, Tax, sales to veterinarians, 1968; nam_apap279-2_63 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - S. 4041, Conserv, timber harvesters, 1968; nam_apap279-2_64 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - S. 4578, Penal., bail jumping, define, 1968; nam_apap279-2_65 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - S. 4581, Penal, unlawful collect. Practice, 1968; nam_apap279-2_66 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - S. 4582, Penal, public lewdness, 1968; nam_apap279-2_67 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - S. 5506 Committee on Rules, Town of Babylon, 1968; nam_apap279-2_68 (Box 11, Folder 38)